{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Advanced Systems Integration and Architecture",
    "Term": "Prelims",
    "Title": "Human Capital Management (HCM)",
    "LastModified": "19 September 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "02_Handout_1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "Which is a variety of practices and applications used for recruiting, managing, and developing an organization’s human capital or workforce?",
      "answer": "Human Capital Management (HCM)",
      "choices": [
        "Human Capital Management (HCM)",
        "Manager Self-Service (MSS)",
        "Enterprise Structure",
        "Organizational Plan"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which represents the structural and personnel organization of a company, consisting of organization units. It illustrates hierarchies and an employee's responsibility?",
      "answer": "Organizational Structure",
      "choices": [
        "Organizational Structure",
        "Enterprise Structure",
        "Personnel Structure",
        "Organizational Plan"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which represents a company area differentiated between personnel administrative, time management, and expensive organizational aspects?",
      "answer": "Personnel Area",
      "choices": [
        "Personnel Area",
        "Personnel Subarea",
        "Personnel Structure",
        "Employee Group"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which represents part of a personnel area and represents a company area differentiated between personnel administration, time management, and payroll accounting aspects?",
      "answer": "Personnel Subarea",
      "choices": [
        "Personnel Area",
        "Personnel Subarea",
        "Personnel Structure",
        "Employee Group"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which describes an employee’s position within the company. It is defined by employee group and employee subgroup?",
      "answer": "Personnel Structure",
      "choices": [
        "Personnel Area",
        "Personnel Subarea",
        "Personnel Structure",
        "Employee Group"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is an organizational unit for which personnel-related regulations can be specified such as active employees, external, and retirees?",
      "answer": "Employee Group",
      "choices": [
        "Employee Group",
        "Employee Subgroup",
        "Personnel Subarea",
        "Personnel Area"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is an organizational unit within the employee group for which personnel-related regulations are specified, such as industrial employees, commercial clerks, and laboratory assistants?",
      "answer": "Employee Subgroup",
      "choices": [
        "Employee Group",
        "Employee Subgroup",
        "Personnel Subarea",
        "Personnel Area"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is an example of Employee Group?",
      "answer": "Retiree",
      "choices": [
        "Internal",
        "Trainee",
        "Employee",
        "Retiree"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is an example of Employee Subroup?",
      "answer": "Employee",
      "choices": [
        "Active",
        "Employee",
        "External",
        "Retiree"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which describes in which function an employee is acting. It is object-oriented, and each element is represented by an object which can be assigned to each other?",
      "answer": "Organizational Plan",
      "choices": [
        "Organizational Structure",
        "Enterprise Structure",
        "Personnel Structure",
        "Organizational Plan"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which can be grouped according to functional and regional aspects?",
      "answer": "Organizational Unit",
      "choices": [
        "Organizational Unit",
        "Position",
        "Person",
        "Cost Center"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is assigned to organizational units and filled by employees such as accounting clerks in the Accounting Department?",
      "answer": "Position",
      "choices": [
        "Organizational Unit",
        "Position",
        "Person",
        "Job"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the employee who fills positions?",
      "answer": "Person",
      "choices": [
        "Internal",
        "External",
        "Person",
        "Active"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which originates from SAP Controlling and can be linked with positions or organizational units?",
      "answer": "Cost Center",
      "choices": [
        "Organizational Unit",
        "Position",
        "Person",
        "Cost Center"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is general description of tasks an employee must perform, such as the position of the Head of Department?",
      "answer": "Job",
      "choices": [
        "Organizational Unit",
        "Position",
        "Person",
        "Job"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the central employee identifier in SAP assigned by the system or manually and comprises up to eight (8) digits?",
      "answer": "Personnel Number",
      "choices": [
        "Personnel Number",
        "Reference Personnel Number",
        "InfoTypes",
        "Personnel Administration"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which helps map different contractual relationships and recreates an existing employee in the system with a new personnel number?",
      "answer": "Reference Personnel Number",
      "choices": [
        "Personnel Number",
        "Reference Personnel Number",
        "InfoTypes",
        "Personnel Administration"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which are collections of logically linked data fields wherein HR master data are structured and process employee data in an effective structure based on business requirements?",
      "answer": "InfoTypes",
      "choices": [
        "Personnel Number",
        "Reference Personnel Number",
        "InfoTypes",
        "Personnel Administration"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is not a characteristic of InfoTypes?",
      "answer": "plausibility checks",
      "choices": [
        "plausibility checks",
        "Has sub-types representing a sub-variant of the InfoType",
        "Time-dependent",
        "Personnel action, and Single InfoType Maintenance"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the first step of SAP HCM processes?",
      "answer": "Organizational Management",
      "choices": [
        "Organizational Management",
        "Personnel Administration",
        "Recruitment",
        "Talent Management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the last step of SAP HCM processes?",
      "answer": "Employee Self-Service (ESS)/Manager SelfService (MSS)",
      "choices": [
        "Employee Self-Service (ESS)/Manager SelfService (MSS)",
        "Personnel Controlling",
        "Performance Management",
        "Talent Management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which models the organizational structure of the enterprise and also analyzes an organizational unit to define workforce requirements and personnel cost planning?",
      "answer": "Organizational Management",
      "choices": [
        "Organizational Management",
        "Personnel Administration",
        "Recruitment",
        "Organizational Plan"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is not a function of Organizational Management?",
      "answer": "Create, change, and delimit persons",
      "choices": [
        "Create, change, and delimit persons",
        "Create, change, and delimit jobs",
        "Create, change, and delimit positions",
        "Create, change, and delimit organizational units"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is concerned with creating and maintaining personnel master data and sets the data basis for other processes in Human Resource Management and reporting?",
      "answer": "Personnel Administration",
      "choices": [
        "Organizational Management",
        "Personnel Administration",
        "Recruitment",
        "Organizational Plan"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is to detect errors and prevent incorrect data transfer.",
      "answer": "plausibility checks",
      "choices": [
        "plausibility checks",
        "automatic history",
        "fraud check",
        "error management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is created when changing master data for reporting and verification of data integrity.",
      "answer": "automatic history",
      "choices": [
        "plausibility checks",
        "automatic history",
        "fraud check",
        "error management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which process objective is to employ personnel with all the required qualifications?",
      "answer": "Recruitment",
      "choices": [
        "Recruitment",
        "Personnel Administration",
        "Personnel Development",
        "Talent Management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the 2 types of recruitment?",
      "answer": "external and internal",
      "choices": [
        "external and internal",
        "employee group and employee subgroup",
        "active and inactive",
        "active and retiree"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "The goal of _______ to support the HR department in searching, choosing, and recruiting adequate applicants?",
      "answer": "Recruitment",
      "choices": [
        "Recruitment",
        "Personnel Administration",
        "Personnel Development",
        "Talent Management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "A database for applicants is developed in this process, including the administration of vacant positions.",
      "answer": "Recruitment Process",
      "choices": [
        "Recruitment Process",
        "Personnel Administration",
        "Personnel Development",
        "Talent Management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Maintaining applicant data is done in _____ using the Initial Data Entry or Application Actions in SAP Fiori",
      "answer": "InfoTypes",
      "choices": [
        "InfoTypes",
        "DataTypes",
        "plausibility checks",
        "Talent Management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which structures applicants based on their employment relationship type?",
      "answer": "Applicant Group",
      "choices": [
        "Applicant Group",
        "Applicant Range",
        "Employee Group",
        "Employee Subgroup"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which classifies applicants based on hierarchical or functional criteria?",
      "answer": "Applicant Range",
      "choices": [
        "Applicant Group",
        "Applicant Range",
        "Employee Group",
        "Employee Subgroup"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which lets every registered applicant partake in the selection procedure?",
      "answer": "Global Selection Procedure",
      "choices": [
        "Global Selection Procedure",
        "Multi Selection Procedure",
        "Single Selection Procedure",
        "Selection Procedure for Every Vacancy"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which selection procedure indicates that the applicant is assigned only to special vacancies?",
      "answer": "Selection Procedure for Every Vacancy",
      "choices": [
        "Global Selection Procedure",
        "Multi Selection Procedure",
        "Single Selection Procedure",
        "Selection Procedure for Every Vacancy"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Its goal is to qualify employees for current and future needs and provide long-term employee benefits",
      "answer": "Personnel Development",
      "choices": [
        "Talent Management",
        "Personnel Development",
        "Qualification",
        "Requirements"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which can be connected to persons or positions and needs to be attached to attributes. It can have a half-life period or a validity period?",
      "answer": "Qualification",
      "choices": [
        "Talent Management",
        "Personnel Development",
        "Qualification",
        "Requirements"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which are qualifications, knowledge, and experiences that can be attached to positions and is created with a characteristic?",
      "answer": "Requirements",
      "choices": [
        "Talent Management",
        "Personnel Development",
        "Qualification",
        "Requirements"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is when a comparison is made between employee qualifications and the position requirements in this proces.",
      "answer": "Profile Matchup",
      "choices": [
        "Profile Matchup",
        "Recruitment",
        "Qualification",
        "Talent Management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a process involves career planning arrangements and succession planning accomplishments and generates general and individual development plans.",
      "answer": "Talent Management",
      "choices": [
        "Career Planning",
        "Succession Planning",
        "Performance Management",
        "Talent Management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which identifies career goals such as by defining and developing special stations of a career (job, position, and course of instruction) and includes comparing qualifications with requirements of one station of a career to personnel decisions and courses of instruction?",
      "answer": "Career Planning",
      "choices": [
        "Career Planning",
        "Succession Planning",
        "Performance Management",
        "Talent Management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which assures continuity in personnel allocation for key positions and includes proactive search for candidates to reallocate key positions?",
      "answer": "Succession Planning",
      "choices": [
        "Career Planning",
        "Succession Planning",
        "Performance Management",
        "Talent Management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which summarize teaching and other educational actions to achieve special qualifications?",
      "answer": "Development Plans",
      "choices": [
        "Career Planning",
        "Development Plans",
        "Performance Management",
        "Talent Management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which defines the objective setting between the enterprise and employees and evaluates the benefits of employees to form feedback used to answer whether the goals are achieved?",
      "answer": "Performance Management",
      "choices": [
        "Career Planning",
        "Development Plans",
        "Performance Management",
        "Talent Management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "An appraisal template has been created and provided with header data. The appraisal template consists of formulas, criteria groups, criteria, and qualifications.",
      "answer": "In Preparation",
      "choices": [
        "In Preparation",
        "In Process",
        "Completed",
        "Approved"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "An appraisal has been given but it is not completed; the evaluation may still be changed.",
      "answer": "In Process",
      "choices": [
        "In Preparation",
        "In Process",
        "Completed",
        "Approved"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "The appraisal is finished.",
      "answer": "Completed",
      "choices": [
        "Rejected",
        "In Process",
        "Completed",
        "Approved"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which enables the creation of reports from a flood of data within Human Resource Management (HRM) and ata needed for a report can arise from a single or several HR processes?",
      "answer": "Personnel Controlling",
      "choices": [
        "Career Planning",
        "Development Plans",
        "Personnel Controlling",
        "Talent Management"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which are predefined SAP requests with a unique design like employee and birthday lists?",
      "answer": "Standard Reports",
      "choices": [
        "Standard Reports",
        "Human Resource Information System (HIS)",
        "Manager’s Desktop (MDT)",
        "Ad-hoc Query"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which enables analysis based on the organizational structure?",
      "answer": "Human Resource Information System (HIS)",
      "choices": [
        "Standard Reports",
        "Human Resource Information System (HIS)",
        "Manager’s Desktop (MDT)",
        "Ad-hoc Query"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which indicates that managers can access transactions of other HCM module components?",
      "answer": "Manager’s Desktop (MDT)",
      "choices": [
        "Standard Reports",
        "Human Resource Information System (HIS)",
        "Manager’s Desktop (MDT)",
        "Ad-hoc Query"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is a tool for analyzing data from personnel management and outside the HCM module?",
      "answer": "Ad-hoc Query",
      "choices": [
        "Business Intelligence (BI)",
        "Human Resource Information System (HIS)",
        "Manager’s Desktop (MDT)",
        "Ad-hoc Query"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is an independent system based on a portal technology and helps data from SAP systems or from other systems to be integrated?",
      "answer": "Business Intelligence (BI)",
      "choices": [
        "Business Intelligence (BI)",
        "Human Resource Information System (HIS)",
        "Manager’s Desktop (MDT)",
        "Ad-hoc Query"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is a web-based user interface for employees that enables the time and location-independent maintenance of personal data?",
      "answer": "Employee Self-Service (ESS)",
      "choices": [
        "Employee Self-Service (ESS)",
        "Manager Self-Service (MSS)",
        "Human Resource Information System (HIS)",
        "Manager’s Desktop (MDT)"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is a central web-based access point for manager and uses the backend systems of the human resources and finance departments and supports the management?",
      "answer": "Manager Self-Service (MSS)",
      "choices": [
        "Employee Self-Service (ESS)",
        "Manager Self-Service (MSS)",
        "Human Resource Information System (HIS)",
        "Manager’s Desktop (MDT)"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following activity can employees perform using ESS?",
      "answer": "Submitting travel expenses",
      "choices": [
        "Submitting travel expenses",
        "Gaining Information",
        "Hiring employees",
        "Controlling costs"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following activity can managers perform using MSS?",
      "answer": "Hiring employees",
      "choices": [
        "Browsing the employee directory",
        "Hiring employees",
        "Applying for employer benefits",
        "Registering for training courses"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    }
  ]
}
